[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the 6th rule of Fight Club in the self-titled movie?", "correct_answer": "No shirts, no shoes.", "incorrect_answers": ["If this is your first night, you have to fight.", "You do not talk about Fight Club.", "Fights go on as long as they have to."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person wrote HTTP, the language in which browsers and web servers communicate.", "correct_answer": "Tim Berners-Lee", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Jobs", "Bill Gates", "Douglas Engelbart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These two brothers personally wrote and directed the movies, Matrix (1999), Matrix Reloaded (2003) and Matrix Revolutions (2003).", "correct_answer": "The Wachowski Brothers", "incorrect_answers": ["The Spierig Brothers", "The Osmond Brothers", "The Quay Brothers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the popular set of optimal rules for playing Blackjack called?", "correct_answer": "Basic strategy", "incorrect_answers": ["Golden rules strategy", "Best strategy", "Push strategy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following has the most fat?", "correct_answer": "American Blue Cheese", "incorrect_answers": ["Cottage Cheese", "Feta", "Parmesan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The temperature of large bodies of water tends to vary much less, compared to that of land masses, why?", "correct_answer": "Water can absorb a tremendous amount of heat", "incorrect_answers": ["Liquids are better heat conductors", "Water responds more quickly to temperature changes", "Sunlight penetrates water more easily"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The peach tree belongs to the Prunus genus which is indigenous to this country.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Morocco", "Argentina", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Ottoman Empire used to rule over North Africa, the Middle East and south-eastern Europe. Which modern day country is the successor of the empire?", "correct_answer": "Turkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Israel", "Saudi Arabia", "Egypt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Crocodiles sex is determined by the temperature of their nest.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1986 movie won the Razzie Award for Worst Picture?", "correct_answer": "Under the Cherry Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["Shanghai Surprise", "Blue City", "Cobra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Italian climber, who was in the first expedition to reach Mount Everest without oxygen tanks, later became the first person to climb the summit alone.", "correct_answer": "Reinhold Messner", "incorrect_answers": ["Laurie Skreslet", "Jerzy Kukuczka", "Tim Macartney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Some small spider species, as well as the young of larger species, are known for floating in the wind. What is this activity commonly known as?", "correct_answer": "Ballooning", "incorrect_answers": ["Skydiving", "Jetting", "Drifting"]}]